Hey guys my name is Balram and I am a
Certified Investment Advisor welcome to all of you in
our
[sangeet]
A marginal sell off was seen in APE 500
whereas due to short covering in N we
can see it trading at 13192 levels here. Currently US Dollar is
trading at 73.9 against Indian Rupee and we can see crude oil
trading above $65 here.
Gold is still falling
and we can
see it trading near $40 here.
Due to this you can
see a short covering in Asian market today
because we can see Singapore based A Nifty
trading near 14000 740 here
and even
Nifty futures can also be
seen near this level here.
After this if we look at APE levels then
in most of the cases you will see a sell off
but if today
due to short covering in the market it is trading at
14700 here  If it opens higher, you should
avoid taking any short trades initially.
In the cash market, we can
see FIs making net sales of around Rs 8,295 crore on the last trading day,
while DIIs are seen using Rs
1,500 crore in the market for buying purposes.
If we look at derivatives,
we see an overall fund outflow of Rs 1,397 crore.
However,
today you may see a slight upside here.
After this, if we
look at the overall market outlook, and that
too from the point of view of futures and options,
then Nifty's March futures can be
seen above around 14,565. Currently,
we can see the Nifty's put and call ratio at around 1.66. So,
today the market may open gap here
and you may get good buying opportunities here.
Finally, if we
talk about some trending  Regarding stocks,
Indian Oil has announced to use around ₹
3246 crore to expand its Panipat refinery capacity
and you can see this thing getting completed
in the next few periods i.e. in the next few
years.
L India is planning to raise
a fund of around ₹1080 crore in its board meeting,
due to which you
can see a record upside in the stock today.
Reliance 1, which is an automotive company and
works on zero emission, has
issued an announcement to take its majority stake here.
If we talk about DLF, it has issued an announcement to
raise a fund of around ₹395 crore from the market with the help of its non-convertibles.
After this,
if we look at Hindustan Aeronaut,
after the announcement of its Q3 results,
this time it has declared a dividend of ₹1 per share here.  It has been announced
here for the shareholders,
due to which
you may see an upside in the stock.
Tel Corporation has been
given three orders worth ₹105.8 crore by the Government of India, and
you may see these orders getting completed in the next 18 months.
This has been announced by the Ministry of Railways. So,
you should avoid booking any profit in the stock today.
In the case of Tel Corporation,
Nippon India and Goldman Sachs have made
a record buying in it. So, you should watch
this stock today on
Acumatica
channel and hit the bell icon. So that you will never miss any
update once we upload our
video and make sure you join our t gra
group where we provide real time market
updates every single day till then I will see
you in the next one and thanks for watching.